H.R. Johnson

Community-Driven in Kalamazoo, Michigan 360-951-0354

find.serendipity@gmail.com & amazonxprincezz@yahoo.com github.com/Find-Serendipity & linkedin.com/in/findserendipity

Summary

Experienced professional with 10+ years in customer service and community management. Excellent communication and interpersonal skills, with a commitment to excellence and attention to detail. Adherent to high standards while working to understand, meet, and exceed guest expectations.

Skills

Languages || French (Intermediate Proficiency), JavaScript, SQL

Tools & Technologies | Hootsuite, Canva, Zendesk, Jira, HubSpot CRM, Apps Scripts

Experience

Air Zoo Aerospace & Science Museum, Kalamazoo, MI \parallel Guest Experience Ambassador Aug 24 – Current

- Guided guests through museum experience while operating from a stationary assignment.
- Engaged with guests, provide information about artifacts at the museum, and correctly answer guest questions.
- Helped manage flow of crowds, efficiently helping guests with needs and directing as needed.
- Ensured guest safety in various situations with various crowd sizes.

Communitrix, Remote | Founder

Sep 2023 – Present

- Drafted and implemented custom community plans for clients.
- Maintained client Shopify site and codebase for client's website.
- Created written and visial media content for client social media.

Community.co, Remote | Community Manager

July 2019 - June 2023

- Managed VIP, CEO, and Influencer publishing and community events.
- Increased community activity from 2% to 7% through strategic initiatives.
- Supervised and trained team members in community tactics and reporting.

Internet Brands, Remote | Community Manager

July 2013 – July 2019

- Upsold \$500,000 worth of online memberships through direct communications.
- Managed cross-functional teams in community forum moderation and customer service.
- Assisted with project management, product development and social media content creation.
- Increased customer satisfaction from 61% to 96%.
- Handled escalated customer support issues and abuse reports.

ModSquad, Remote | Social Media Strategist

Aug 2010 – Feb 2012

- Executed social media strategies pursuant to client requests and needs.
- Provided concierge-level customer service and online moderation services.

Education

Fullstack Academy, Remote | Junior Developer

Feb 2024 - June 2024

- Top-ranking graduate of the online full-time full-stack web development bootcamp.
- Learned advanced web engineering through hands-on projects and coursework.

University of Washington, Seattle | Bachelor of Arts in Anthropology

2011

- Top-ranking graduate, Summa cum laude
- Focused on Archaeology, Anthropology, Oceanography, Geology